[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":81215,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":93111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":9141,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":102257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":23521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":125782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2752,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":128536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":134441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2384,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":136831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second  one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":11682,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":148514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1686,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":150201,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6586,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":156788,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1666,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":158456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3698,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":162156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub> 6</sub>  0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":2668,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":164825,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4671,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":169497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1823,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":171326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br / ><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4413,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":175741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1629,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":177372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your res ult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":181853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1474,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":183328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3516,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":186846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1420,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":188267,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3401,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":191669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1423,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":193094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":23825,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":216926,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inv erse und er +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":27579,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":244507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":12674,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":257184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2171,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":259357,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br />  (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":8367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":267726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1666,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":269394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3707,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":273103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1628,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":274733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3964,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":278699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity unde r +<sub> 6</sub>.","rt":1666,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":280366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":12547,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":292914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4086,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":297003,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can sim ply be p erformed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":19398,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":316402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</s ub> 2, b ut there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":620457,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":936862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":10253,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":947126,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1711,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":948840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><b r /> (Re member, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":952217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":6696,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":958917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</s ub>? <br  /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":965743,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1597,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":967342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6360,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":973704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1512,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":975218,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question w ith feed back to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":23497,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":998717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5661,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1004379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1524,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1005905,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3621,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1009527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4698,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1014226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1017123,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2888,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1020012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3992,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1024005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":14964,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1038970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4 +1 = 5 and that is less than 9 so it is left alone","explanation_history":["4 +1 = 5 and that is less than 9 so it is left alone"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":27510,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1066481,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"2","explain":true,"explanation":"8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subtract 9 and you are left with 2","explanation_history":["8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subrr","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subract ","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subract","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 s o subrac ","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subra","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subr","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subtract 98 a","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subtract 98 ","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subtract 98","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subtract 9 an ","8 plus 4 is 12 and that is more than 9 so subtract 9 and you are left with 2"],"response_history":["2"],"rt":35881,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1102365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"8","explain":true,"explanation":"8 added to 1 is 9 ","explanation_history":["8 added to 1 is ni","8 added to 1 is n","8 added to 1 is 9 a","8 added to 1 is 9 "],"response_history":["8"],"rt":48244,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1150611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":13459,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1164072,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":19785,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1183858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2803,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1186662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"1","explain":true,"explanation":"I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse. ","explanation_history":["I am ","I am","I a","I have confused myself and not real sure abou th","I have confused myself and not real sure abou t","I have confused myself and not real sure abou ","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse/; ","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse/;","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse/","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse. One is","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse. One i","I have confused myself and not real sure abo ut the i nverse. One ","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse. One","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse. On","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse. O","I have confused myself and not real sure about the inverse. "],"response_history":["1"],"rt":35656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1222319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"you can't add two to every number to get 9","explanation_history":["you can't add two to every number to get 9"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":21645,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1243966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explai n in wor ds how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"you can add 3 to a number to get 9","explanation_history":["you can't add 3 to ","ye","y","you can add 3 to a number to get 9"],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":38494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1282463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"you can add 5 to a number to get 9","explanation_history":["you can add 5 to a number to get 9"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":12683,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1295147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please ex plain in  words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"yes you can add 6 to a number and get 9","explanation_history":["yes you can get ","yes you can get","yes you can ge","yes you can ga","yes you can g","yes you can add 65 ","yes you can add 65","yes you can add 6 to a number and get 9"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":21636,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1316784,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":388215,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1705003,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"you have lost me","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["you have lost me"],"rt":31335,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1736348,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"?","explain":true,"explanation":"i am sorry you have lost me","explanation_history":["i am sorryt ","i am sorryt","i am sorry you have lost me"],"response_history":["?"],"rt":34305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1770659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern  to which  elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am lost","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I am lost"],"rt":9499,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1780160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":9023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1789184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"mult i","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":4107,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1793293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":8309,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1801603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","Fal se"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"i don't know","explanation_history":["i don't know"],"response_history":["True"],"rt":27382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1828990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6992,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1835985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"just seems what might be the right answer. You have lost me","explanation_history":["just seems tht","just seems th","just seems t","just seems t","just seems wht","just seems what might be thr","just seems what might be the e","just seems what might be the right answer. I ","just seems what might be the right answer. I","just seems what might be the right answer. You have lost me"],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":20758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1856744,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1860784,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1551,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1862337,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"48","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["48"],"rt":2763,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1865101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, n o degree ","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2827,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1867930,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Advnaced","Advnace","Advnac","Advna","Advn","Advanced Business Math. ","Advanced Business Math.","Advanced Business Math, Alger","Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, Advanced accou","Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, Advance","Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, Advanc","Advanced Business Math, Algebra  II, Adva n","Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, Adva","Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, Adv","Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, Ad","Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, A","Advanced Business Math, Algebra II, "],"rt":37560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1905491,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4051,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1909549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a  mathemat ical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":9069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1918620,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1923336,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you  underst ood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1928463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3505,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1931969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2601,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1934571,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":4392,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1938964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":4190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1943155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments o n this H IT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I tried and wanted to do good. But at some point I got lost. I am sorry ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I tried and wanted to to do","I tried and wanted to to d","I tried and wanted to to ","I tried and wanted to to","I tried and wanted to t","I tried and wanted to do good. But at some pon","I tried and wanted to do good. But at some point I got lost. I am sorry "],"rt":21038,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1964194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]